

NUR FARHANA ROSENI

+6013-503 0520 farhanaroseni@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/farhanaroseni https://farhanaroseni.github.io Ipoh, Perak, Malaysia

OBJECTIVE

Detail-oriented professional with over 2 years of experience in advanced analytics at a global market research company. After a career break for self-development, I am now eager to contribute my skills to a position related to analytics in your organization. Explore my work at *farhanaroseni.github.io* for examples of data analysis and visualization projects. I am **open to relocation** for the right job opportunity and **available to start working immediately**.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DATA SCIENTIST | GMU Advanced Analytics, Ipsos Sdn Bhd | May 2021 - Dec 2023

- Conducted comprehensive data analysis on large data sets to extract meaningful insights and patterns which help the client in their decision-making processes
- Applied advanced analytical techniques, including cohort analysis, retention analysis, behavioral profiling, pre-post analysis, and longitudinal analysis
- Collaborated closely with client service teams from UK to understand client's business objective
- Developed clear and concise documentation that significantly reduced the time required for clients to identify relevant analyses, fostering efficiency in decision-making processes
- Successfully delivered results within short turnaround times for one of the biggest client in the UK
- Acquired skills in Tableau within one months and successfully provide support to Tableau team during periods of resource constraints contributing to the completion of projects without compromising on quality or timelines
- Awarded "Spark Award 2023" for demonstrating values of Integrity and Client First

INDUSTRIAL TRAINING | Finance Department, Majlis Agama Islam Dan 'Adat Melayu Perak | Oct 2020 - Jan 2021

- Facilitated in registering received payment voucher in the e-SPB Audit System
- Responsible for maintaining filing system by organizing all the completed received payment voucher in the file folders accurately

EDUCATION

UITM MACHANG CAMPUS | Bachelor of Science (Hons.) Mathematics | 2017 - 2021

- Faculty of Computer and Mathematical Sciences
- Major in Mathematics and Minor in Accounting
- Final CGPA: 3.92
- Graduation Year: 2021

UITM DENGKIL | Foundation in Science | 2016 - 2017

- Obtained a Final CGPA of 3.89
- Achieved Band 4 in Malaysian University English Test (MUET) November 2016

SBP INTEGRASI GOPENG | Pure Science Stream | 2014 - 2015

Obtained 7As in SPM Year 2015

INVOLVEMENT & LEADERSHIP

Committee Members for Ipsos Annual Dinner 2022 | Dec 2022

Managed specific responsibilities, such as designed the event's ticket and assisted the registration process which resulting in a well-organized events.

Participated in Beijing Foreign Studies University (BFSU) Summer Camp Program 2019 at Beijing, China | Jul 2019 – Aug 2019

A two weeks program organized by Kong Zi Institute University of Malaya that gives students the opportunity to gain personal experience with Chinese language and culture.

Secretariat of Student Representative Council | Sept 2017 - Sept 2018

Assists Student Representative Council managed events for students of UiTM Machang Campus such as Ekspo Kelab dan Persatuan which is an annual event that gives chance to all the clubs and associations to approached new students.

Committee Members (Event Manager) for Festival Malaysia 2018 | Sept 2018

A collaboration event organized by Student Representative Council and other student leader of UiTM Machang Campus with more than 20 activities, programs and sales booth. Acted as event manager which responsible in planning and ensuring all activities and programs run smoothly throughout the festival.

SKILLS

Software Skills

MS Word, MS Excel, MS PowerPoint SPSS, Tableau, Python, SQL, Power BI, C++, R

Languages

Bahasa Melayu and English

AWARDS

- Ipsos Spark Award 2023 for demonstrating values of Integrity and Client First
- Dean's List Award for Undergraduate Study
- Vice Chancellor Award for Undergraduate Study